hospital
[music]
over the years. Medical science and
health infrastructure.
World class hospital
insurance.
Health insurance.
[music]
So
health insurance.
Welcome to
health insurance
company profile and reputation
insurance
first standalone health insurer Star
Health backed by HTFC bank regroup
health focus health insurance
known for it strong digital claim
system.
Tier two, tier three cities.
So company profile and reputation
healthfal
settlement and customer experience
claim settlement ratio HTFC approximate
97%
85%
complaints
complaints HTFC
reimbursement claim time
insurance.
Once we submit all the documents,
SoFC
health on the other handlement
ratiocience
compar
So insurance flagships
[music]
HTFC%
related and unrelated
and post
Example,
hospitalization
insurance
60 days prehospization
post hospitalization hospitalization
Starf
hospitalization 180 days
rent no capraf
Departmentistered
Insurance,
OPD, outpatient, dental
cover,
HTFC FC
health insurance
consent
document
freeze age benefit
in case for
insurance
premiums particular health Insurance
freeze age benefit.
You can lock premium if no claims are
done.
comparison
[music] nonmandatory freeze age benefit
in case
premiums particular health insurance
freeze age limit. Freeze age benefit.
You can lock premium if no claims are
done. So
comparison
nonmandatory. So particular
star more of lifestyle friendly
hospitalization
options.
So
star health superstar premium
HTFC
approximat
Health
approximal
health insurance. Okay.
features
and at the same time HDFC
claimment
emergency.
So in the point
health insurance
information
free consultation
certified experts
free consultation.
First
options
clarification
So
avail. availability.
And once
24 bar 7 claim assistance
health insurance
back topic
HDFC and Star Health
Network Hospitals in Tamiladas
all
widest network
hospitals
where you can get cashless treatment
strong. So star network
across 1,200 plus hospitals network
treat
Star Health
compared to HTFC
waiting period
threeear waiting period for pre-existing
disease pre-existing disease already
waiting period star health and HDFC
so
both no disease wise sublims. So
disease wise
freeze ageenefit.
HDFC.
So, HTFC
customer service
digital portal
quickanch
So in case
support
line and
final recommendation
First star
for examp
So
options features
high
and fast cash treatment.
fortrifiable.
For example,
Health infrastructure, medical science,
advanced treatments.
foreign.
So
health insurance
end of the day
insurance
be the boss.